<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DC33 on The Official DEF CON Networking Team</title>
    <link>https://noc.defcon.org/tags/dc33/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DC33 on The Official DEF CON Networking Team</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 09:19:41 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://noc.defcon.org/tags/dc33/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DEF CON 33 More Stats</title>
      <link>https://noc.defcon.org/posts/dc33/dc33-wifi-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 09:19:41 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noc.defcon.org/posts/dc33/dc33-wifi-stats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DEF CON 33 - Here&amp;rsquo;s some data&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year, sparky and mac wanted to start sharing a bit more of what we do and how things go behind the scene. In that sense, I am going to throw at you a lot of boring numbers, charts&amp;hellip; and some fun stuff we did this year.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First we do the work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Like mac mentioned on his post, this year we knew beforehand that we would have less time to setup everything. So we had to be creative and come up with ways to reduce our setup time, and one of those ideas was to use wireless bridges to significantly reduce the number of physical drops we had to run all over the convention center.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEF CON 33 Network - Infrastructure Summmary Report</title>
      <link>https://noc.defcon.org/posts/dc33/dc33-eol-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noc.defcon.org/posts/dc33/dc33-eol-stats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welp, another year, another DEF CON come and gone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the whole, it was a big success for the DEF CON NOC. We tried out a few new&#xA;things that went well. The biggest one was some wireless bridges. For&#xA;&lt;em&gt;reasons&lt;/em&gt;, we had a shortened on site setup time, so we really had to cut down&#xA;our install time. Mostly this meant cutting down on the number of floor wired&#xA;drops that we could provide or providing them in a much fast way. We opted for&#xA;the second option by providing some wireless bridges. We&amp;rsquo;ll put up a post later&#xA;with the specifics of these, but all in all, we think they did the job.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEF CON 33 Post-Con Stats Are Coming</title>
      <link>https://noc.defcon.org/posts/dc33/dc33-eol-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 15:24:15 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://noc.defcon.org/posts/dc33/dc33-eol-coming/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://noc.defcon.org/media/dc33-coming.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;dc33 stats are coming&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
